{
    "subject": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Carnival_in_Flanders__film_",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Feyder directed the film Carnival in Flanders.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9335747361183167,
            "question": "Who directed the film Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8564346432685852,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7783178091049194,
            "question": "What other films has Jacques Feyder directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6638560891151428,
            "question": "Was Carnival in Flanders a popular film upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5736587047576904,
            "question": "What genre might the film Carnival in Flanders belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5678906440734863,
            "question": "Where was Carnival in Flanders likely filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.560998797416687,
            "question": "What is Jacques Feyder known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5092028975486755,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5006592869758606,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the film Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42343711853027344,
            "question": "Has Carnival in Flanders been remade or adapted?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Feyder directed the film Carnival in Flanders.",
            "html": "yago_8590_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the film Carnival in Flanders?",
            "html": "yago_8590_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Carnival in Flanders?",
            "html": "yago_8590_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jacques Feyder known for?",
            "html": "yago_8590_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8590_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text explicitly states that the film \"Carnival in Flanders\" was directed by Jacques Feyder, and it also mentions the same film multiple times throughout the provided context."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that confirm Jacques Feyder directed the film \"Carnival in Flanders\" (1935), including statements from various articles and overviews."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}